In 1929, the Hungarian writer Frigyes Karinthy
1929年，匈牙利作家Frigyes Karinthy
wrote in his short story CHAINS
在短篇小说锁链中写道
that a person tries to reach a designated person he doesn't know
一个人试图通过不超过五个的中间人
through no more than five intermediaries
来联系一个指定的陌生人
which is the origin of six degrees of separation
这便是六度分隔理论的起源
In the Small-world experiment 1960s
在二十世纪六十年代的小世界实验中
Stanley Milgram and other researchers
Stanley Milgram和其他研究者们
examining the average path length for social networks
检定美国人均社交网络路径
of people in the United States is around 6
长度为六
However, the experiment was not completely randomized and idealized
然而，该实验的设定不够随机又不够理想
It was not until 1998 that Duncan Watts and Steven Strogatz
直到1998年，Duncan Watts和Steven Strogatz
published the first network model on the small-world phenomenon
才发表了关于小世界现象的第一个网络模型
And this mathematical model has since been applied
而后来，这个数学模型
in a wide range of different areas
被广泛地应用在了不同的领域
Today, it is much easier to test the model with social network datasets.
如今，用社交网络数据集来测试该模型就容易多了
We seek to validate the small-world network properties of Twitter
我们试图从网络科学出发
by analysing datasets from the its network
通过对推特网络的数据集进行分析
from a network science perspective
验证推特的小世界网络属性
This will allow us design a simple recommendation algorithm
从而利用小世界网络的特性
that exploits the features of the small-world network
设计一种简单的推荐算法
to uncover more possibilities
来挖掘更多的可能性
like people you might know
比如可能认识的人
Furthermore, we can implement more valuable features
进一步来说，我们可以
based on that great piece
根据那篇大名鼎鼎的 弱联系的力量
THE STRENGTH OF WEEK TIES
实现更多有价值的功能
So, how will we begin our work?
那么，我们将如何开始？
First we need to download the dataset for this analysis
首先我们需要下载本次所需数据集
Thanks to the work of Hubert Wassner
感谢Hubert Wassner的成果
we can download it directly from the Kaggle website
我们可以直接从Kaggle网站下载
This dataset is over 400MB
这个数据集有400多兆
and contains more than 40,000 rows of data
囊括了四万余行数据
including 10 columns of information such as users ID and followers ID
包含用户ID，粉丝ID等10列信息
They are selected because they tweeted on Twitter trending topics
这些用户被选中是因为他们在推特热门话题里发了推
In order to filter out spam and non-informative accounts
为了过滤掉广告和低质账户
the founder had selected users that have at least 100 followers and followings
创建者将至少拥有100个粉丝和关注的用户筛选出来
Next is Data Preprocessing
接下来我们需要进行数据的预处理
What we should do is to change the data format to some useful dictionaries
我们应该做的是将数据格式改为一些有用的字典
We will use several dictionary for further uses
我们在之后应该就要用到这些字典了
Then we need to build relevant networks
然后是建立相关的网络
We intend to construct a directed graph A
我们打算以用户ID为点
with User IDs as points and the connection list of follower IDs as edges
和粉丝ID的联系为边，构筑有向图A
Next, keep the interrelated edges and construct the undirected graph B
下一步，保留互关的边，构筑无向图B
In the analysis of the network we believe that operations
在对网络的分析中，我们认为
such as computing degrees and clustering are necessary and helpful.
计算degree、聚类等操作是必要且有帮助的
More important is the analysis of the strong and weak ties
比较重要的是对强弱链接的分析
and we initially propose this division
我们初步提出了这个划分方式
As for undirected graph B
而对于无向图B来说
we might be able to find those CONNECTORS
我们或许可以找到那些社牛
people who has large networks of contacts and friends
那些人脉很广，朋友圈很大的人
That's all we have for today
这便是我们今天的内容了
and we hope you all have a good result
希望大家都有一个好的成果